That time rainbow conchitanol to Akita
Hi!
Well then, let's start with greetings, shall we?
Yes, I'm Miyu the Giraffe, a.k.a. Pippi.
Yes, I'm Akari Nakamura aka Akarin
Yes, I'm Moe Tsurumi, a.k.a. Moe-chan.
Yes, I'm Riko Manazuru aka Rikopin
Yes, I'm Karin aka Karin Motooka
Yes, we are the five of us!
Yes, yes!
Now that we've started, here we are!
Why Akita?
With the cooperation of ANA
Mijikon's fan club tour
We went to Akita, right?
That's right.
This time, I'd like to talk about the tour
I'm going to talk about the tour for the official ANA YouTube!
No, no, no...
Yes, yes, yes.
For the channel? Yes, yes, yes!
The same Akita version is also available on the official YouTube channel of Niji no Conquistador, so please check out their channel as well!
First of all, this is the facility where we are filming today!
It's the ANA Blue Base, the training facility of the ANA!
Wow! Thank you!
I've never been here before!
This is a training facility for pilots, flight attendants, and many other professions related to airplanes!
I've already had a glimpse inside!
It's so colorful!
It's an airplane called "Tsoo"!
A plane called "Tsoo"!
Like a simulator!Like a simulator!
It's exciting!
The background is already exciting!
So, this is the Akita part, have you ever been to Akita before?
First time!
This time, we were so happy to be able to fly there by ANA!
Airplanes are so fast!
Yes! Akita used to arrive in such shorts!
So strong!
What did you guys do on the plane?
We drank the famous consomme soup!
We were all really looking forward to it before we left!
We were really looking forward to drinking it, too, and it was so delicious and filling.
Even the girl who was a little bit drowsy said, "Here comes the soup!
Even though she was sleeping, she wanted to drink the soup, so please wake her up! You know, like that.
Everyone worked together and drank the soup.
Then everyone drank the cocoa soup!
I drank it!
But I like apple juice!
I mean, isn't apple juice kind of tasty when you drink it on the plane?
But after I drank about 2 cups, they asked me if they could have some instead. I was so happy and asked if I could have some consommé soup.
I was so happy that I could drink both consommé soup and apple juice.
We were together!
We arrived at Akita Airport on ANA's plane.
Wasn't there anything that made you feel like you were in Akita the moment you entered the airport?
There was a huge bald guy, right?
There it was!
We took a picture in front of it, didn't we?
Yes, yes, yes!
Do you guys know what a live bald spot is?Does everyone know what a fresh bald spot is?
Children...
I have an image of a rather aimekan...
Does everyone have one?
Here's Moe's manager.
What is it?
Nama Hage is an event that has been held around the Oga Peninsula in Akita Prefecture.
It refers to the messengers of the gods who wear masks and straw costumes.
God?
He was a god, so he was God's messenger.
Was he really that great?
That's amazing.
That's a pretty good story.
That's God's food for thought.
That's right.
I'm just a little clumsy.
Let me surprise you.
You're right.
It's important to make an imprint when you're a kid.
I think it's important for God to have an impact.
Maybe that's what I'm getting at.
And one more thing... who remembers the one that appeared at the airport at Chochi?
The ones lined up in a row.
That's right.
Here's Moe's manager.
What a surprise!
I'm so knowledgeable today.
I want to know.
That chouchi is called a Kanto, used in the Akita Kanto festival.
This festival is held every year in August.
They parade around with a big pole and a lot of Kanto on the pole, which they support with their body parts.
Isn't it heavy?Isn't that thing heavy?
You said you were going to put it in here somewhere.
No, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
I mean the space between the clothes.
It's like, can you stand up like this?
Isn't that right?
Wear it on your body.
Yes.
It's like a support.
It's a mess.
But it's really hard to meet people on an expedition.
That's true.
I'd like to go there for that next time.
I want to go there.
I'll look forward to seeing you on the next expedition.
I'll take the liberty of asking.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Now, on to the second day of the Ana trip!
Do you remember when we went to Ituno Date during our free time on the second day of the Anna Trip?
Yes, I remember.
It's a town of elegance.
That's right.
Here's Moe no Mamusho.
Here we go.
Yes.
Itsukuno Date is a popular spot for foreign tourists.
There are many samurai residences.
Samurai residences have been preserved.
It's also called Michi no Ku Shokyo.
Shoukyou
Indeed.Indeed.
We've made it to the middle of the year.
Today, we actually split up into four groups for free time.
Today's group is made up of representatives from each of those four groups.
Each of those four groups had a representative.
And you were the leader?
I was the leader.
It's my group.
I see.
Well, here's what we're going to do.
I'd like to take a look at each team's free time.
OLA-LA-LA.
It's great.
The air is so nice.
It really is.
There's a little snow on the ground.
Here it comes! Yeah!
It's so cute! Look at this!
A cat!
It's a dog!
Doggy!
Anything you want to wear!
Look at this! This looks like him!
I named her!
What?
Dream!
It's Dream!
I love it! A dream!
Yes! A dream!
I don't know where I am.I don't know where I am.
Snow!
It's snowing!
It's snowing more than Tokyo!
Oh, my gosh!
I want to buy a fresh baldness strap!
I wonder if they have fresh bald straps?
Thanks for your hard work!
I'm hungry.
Isn't it too big?
What's this?
Is it too big?
That one.
It's not the same as the one on the right.
It's good, right?
It's totally fine.
Not bad at all.
Here's another one of our regular stores.
What do you think?
Bon appétit.
What do we do? What do we do?
We'll go here.
Or we could go to the pudding place.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go to the pudding place.
I'll see you later.
I'm off.
Let's go to pudding place, No-chan.
There's a really cute and delicious pudding shop.
I love pudding!
I'm going to go there.
But we've got to hurry, we don't have much time, so we're going to walk fast.But we've got to hurry, we don't have much time, so we're going to have to walk fast.
It was so spring and warm.
You didn't have to cheat on your wife.
Yeah, I heard it's so unexpected that you don't do it
The view is so beautiful!
Human car
Bonding, bonding shop.
If we ride this together, won't we bond?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're kidding? Yoo-hoo!
Oh, no, hurry up.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, hurry up.
I don't see anyone running that fast.
Yes, we are.
I knew it.
Really?
Nana...
I don't run.
What? What do you mean you don't have time?
That's why we have a fixed time.
We have to be on the train by a certain time.
It's a stone's throw away.
But tell him it's a train.
What?
He said, "Run.
Run.
Thank you for watching.
Ayanan!
I couldn't run.I couldn't run.
I couldn't run.
Wait a minute!
I can't! I can't!
I can't!
No, they're only going these ways.
I'm walking.
Yoo-hoo!
He's so cute.
Oh, it's huge.
It's so cute.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's too cute.
It's great!
It's just like the little one.
He's so cute!
Hurry up!
We're gonna eat pudding for sure!
You're so cute!
Why do you look so peaceful?
Isn't he huge?
He's so cute!
And he can do that sword thing.
She's so cute!
She's not going to win anything.
That's terrible!
He's already given up!
We're here.
That's it.
That's the one.That's the one.
That's the one. That's the one. That's the one.
It looks good. It looks good.
Hey, everyone's coming for the pudding!
Watch out!
Hot pudding!
I thought it looked really good.
But it's the same as the other one.
Delicious!
Looks delicious.
Wow!
Here's the pudding parfait! Too cute!
It's so cute! It's retro and cute! It's perfect for the city!
The stickers are cute too. It's nostalgic.
I'm going to have a pudding parfait!
Here you go.
Let's try the ice cream.
I wonder what it tastes like.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Mmm!
It's so rich.
It tastes like milk!
Heh heh heh heh.
Then I'll try some too.
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Ah!
Oh, wow.
Amazing.
It's not pudding or pudding, it's soft serve ice cream. It tastes like custard.
It's good, isn't it? - It's good, it's good.It's good. It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Make it. I got up.
It was so big.
Oh, man.
Ta-da! I bought clean software!
And now I'm running!
So this is what it looked like... Everyone was going around.
Let's look at one team at a time, shall we?
The winning team went to the Wagashi-ya once.
The winning team went to the first clean area.
So many people, so many fans.
and talking with them a little bit.
I'm sure this is great," and then we'd go for another walk.
And then we go out for a walk again.
Without buying anything.
And we're taking a walk.
I hear there's one I want to bore you with.
I said, "Well, let's go take a look.
I went for a walk, and there was a gacha
And there was a "I want to be bored" gacha (toy gacha).
Rumble Rumble?
We all played with it together.
We got a dog and a real dog.
and the real one together.
You're a nerd, aren't you?
I'm a nerd messenger.
I'm gonna take a slow walk and stop the clock.
You're clearly discouraged.
What about us?
No, really.No, really.
Moomi-senpai and Meme-me...
They started running so fast.
Nana and I have been walking to the camera
We're running.
And we get tired of it.
We touch each other a little bit.
And in the meantime, we're already very far away from each other.
Moemi and us.
And Shimiko and the others?
We were really...
Walking.
It was like a tour for the fans.
I had to give them attention.
I was looking for you so hard.
We found a dog
found a dog messenger that she wanted to get bored with.
Yes, yes, yes...
You and me.
and the dog who wants to get bored of the mess
and the dog who wants to be bored
Three shots.
I was taking some sewing machine pictures.
And there were a lot of fans
And all the fans were there.
It was a nice gathering.
What about Karin's team?
We heard about the pudding a little late.
We were twice as fast as Moemi and her team.
I was running about twice as fast as Moomi and the others.
I was running about twice as fast.I was running.
But I still got there just in time.
I've been blasting down that road.
Next time, I'll walk a bit and relax
I'd like to go back
I'd like to go back there again
We didn't make it all the way around.
I could have done this for a day.
Let's say so.
I want to go back.
And now, let's continue.
In the afternoon of the second day, we went to the home of the dog that you want to be tired of.
I went to the dog village.
Why is it that...
I wonder why I feel so peaceful when I see them.
Today, too.
Japan is peaceful.
It makes you feel good, doesn't it?
It's the eyes, isn't it?
I know.
Like you're sleeping.
That's right.
Here we go.
Moe Moe's impersonation.
I wasn't paying attention.
I haven't heard it in a while.
It's still there.
I've had enough of that place.
Since it opened in 2019.
More than half a million people have visited
It's a fresh new place
There you go.And there it was.
We took a photo with our fans.
Why?
Well, you know, Mr. Bored Dog...
They didn't write us any notes.
Bored dogs... all of them.
They're so cute!
Take a picture, take a picture!
And the dog who wants to get bored...
I don't know where to look.
It was so sparkly.
Miraculously.
The picture.
I had to work really hard to get him to face the front.
Feeding it.
Like a junkie.
Free time, people.
What were they doing?
They were looking for key chains.
We did a lot of that... collectibles.
I have a favorite character.
I'm tired of it, and I want to be tired of it.
and I wanted a key ring.
I wanted the key chain.
but it was sold out.
I wanted it so bad.
I had to go back and see if they had restocked it.
I have to go back.
But there was something that everyone
There was something that everyone was excited about.
That one.That one.
Who drew the lottery for the dog you want to be bored with?
Who drew the lottery.
How did you all do?
I don't know.
It's not good.
It's so cute when you read it.
I'll take a stuffed animal.
It's a nice size.
Okay, well, watch the VCR here.
I don't want to watch anymore.
Her name's Worms.
Mi-chan.
I've seen a voracious eater's face for a moment now.
What? Why? Why?
Mi-chan, Mi-chan, Mi-chan
Mi-chan, that's nice.
I was just looking at his face and it just came out.
Because it's Shimizu.
And he's really Mr. Shimizu.
Oh, man, I've never laughed so hard in my life.
It's probably the happiest I've ever felt in the next generation.
I'm laughing so hard!
I'm going to live with an Akita dog.
I'll never lose to Moe Tsurumi!
Look forward to seeing what kind of video you'll see next time!
See you soon!
Which one is the cutest?
You're looking at her so hard!
Take her home!
But she just saw me.
Where do you want it?Where do you want it?
This girl asked me to take her home.
I'll take her.
What's her name?
Mochiko.
Mochiko's cute!
Mochiko and worm.
Uncle is cute
Uncle is cute.
ahaha
It's kinda sad
Sad, isn't it?
After seeing that one.
But after seeing mine.
You liked it so much you did it this time, right?
That's right.
And here it is.
Here.
Wow.
There's nothing in the script.
I brought it without being asked.
What?
How far do you dance?
I thought I'd show you.
It's been a while. I'm sure you'd all like to see her.
What's her name?
Daikichi.
What position do you usually keep at home?
At the foot of the bed.
But my sister really likes stuffed animals.But my sister is really into stuffed animals.
She almost took it away from me.
Heh.
You can't have this one, so I'm taking it away.
My stuffed animal.
She's the only one I'm spending money on.
She's cute, too.
I see.
Yes, that's right.
I'd like to send her with you from now on, but...
Yes, she's been here all along.
This time...
Kakuno Date, Akita Edo no Sato and
I looked back on my trip to Akita
What did you think?
How was it?
It's a peaceful place!
Very much so.
It made me want to go back.
Seeing it.
I didn't know anything about it.
So everything was new.
That's for sure.
I was really relaxed.
I mean, I was.
I heard they were doing it inside.
Compared to this place, though.
I didn't even know we were walking.
I was walking.
I want to go back... slowly.
I want to go back.
I want to go backI'd love to go!
Come on, next time Anataby.
In the real dolls
We went to Okinawa too!
In Okinawa
We filmed a music video there.
Well, Okinawa was great too!
It was great!
Yes, it was!
Here's the official ANA YouTube
where we all stayed together.
and episodes from Web5 Okinawa Seragaki.
ANA's
where they store their airplanes.
It's special!
Yes, it is!
We are going to send you the story about the shooting at such a place.
We are planning to send you the story of the filming at such a place.
Please come back and watch the next episode!
Seino
This is Dole, the rainbow's true love!
Bye bye!